Srb, Jozette H. Retirement Studies Research Files /4081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jozette H. Srb Retirement Studies Research Files
1967-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Srb, Jozette H.
/4081
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3085776
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 27, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Srb, Jozetta H.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3085776
- Fudiciary Responsibility, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Erisa - A/C Work Group Repts + Corr., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Erisa - A/C Corresp. Dance, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ERISA + Fiduciary, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ERISA, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ERISA, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ERISA Advisory Council Meeting Nov. 13, 1985 Jozetta SRB (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ERISA, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ERISA Advisory Council Meeting - Jozetta SRB, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Social Investment and The Regulation of Pension Investments: Basic Materials, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1985 Annual Report of the New York State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues (Box 2, Folder 5)
- New York State Department of Social Services SSI State Manual, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Erisa Soley in Whose Interest?, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Women and Aging - A Report on the Rest of Our Lives, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ERISA Advisory Council Meeting June 2 and 3, 1986 Jozetta SRB (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Jozetta H. SRB, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ERISA, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Introduction - Recent Disclosure Case, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ERISA/Coll. B'ging Issues, 1974-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ERISA/ Legislative Work Group, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ERISA/DOL Studies - Misc., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Port/Recipricorty, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ERISA/Progress Reports DOL (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Executive Summary - Pension Plan Terminations with Asset Reversions, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1985-86 ERISA - Adv. Council Termination Task Force, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Jozetta Srb, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ERISA, 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- National Pension Forum of the ERISA Advisory Council Final Report Volume 1, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Department of Labor Contract Number, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Department of Labor Contract Number J0-9-P-4-0092, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Jozetta H. Srb, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Jozetta H. Srb, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Jo Srb, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- The National Pension Forum - ERISA - Jozetta Srb, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Jo Srb, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- News Releases DOL + PBGG, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Pension and Welfare Benefit Programs - ERISA, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- ERISA - A/C DOL Progress Report's - Proceedings (Transcript), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Pres. Com. On Pens., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- New York State Executive Department Office for the Aging, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Comm. Work Group Reports, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- DOL "Services of Information" for policy - makers - Paper Published this file, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Old Age and Ruralism A Case of Double Jeopardy, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Pensions - A Report of the Mayor's Management Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Annual Report of Financial Transactions Public Retirement Systems, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Administrative Expenses of Welfare and Pension Plans, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Report of The Permanent Commission on Public Employee Pension and Retirement Systems, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Pension Reform A Progress Report - Jozetta Srb - Tape, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)